Guide to the Stanford University, Center for Latin American Studies, Records SC0185
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Records, Series 1
  - Research Grants, Subseries 15
    - Johnson, John J.: Latin America Cartoon Research, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Johnson, John J.: Stereotype Research, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Kovacs, Stephen, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Keesing, Donald B. (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Martin, Gerald M., 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Packenham, Robert Grant, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Perlman, Janice, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Reynolds, C1ark, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Reynolds, Clark-Solis, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Stein, Steven, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Wirth, John D., 1972 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Zubrow, Ezra, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Stanford University, Subseries 16
    - Related Departments
      - Center for Research in International Studies (CRIS), General Correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box 8, Folder 71)
      - CRIS, General Information, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 72)
      - CRIS, General Information, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 73)
      - CRIS, General Information, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 74)
      - CRIS, General Information, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 75)
      - CRIS, General Information, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 76)
      - Committee on Foreign Study Programs: Minutes, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 77)
      - CIS Newsletters, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - Professional Schools
      - School of Business, Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Comnunication Research, Institute for: Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - School of Education, 1968-1975 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - School of Education, Stanford International Development Education Center (SIDEC): Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - School of Education, SIDEC: Latin American and Caribbean Development Education Students, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - School of Engineering, 1969-1972 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - School of Law: Correspondence, 1965-1972 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - School of Law: Journal of International Studies, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - School of Medicine: Correspondence, 1967-1971 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - SWOPSI: General Information, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Visitors, Subseries 17
    - Belarinde, Terry Fernando, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Belaunde, Jose, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Biderman, Sol, 1970-72 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Brandenburg, Frank, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Browning, Harley, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Chavez, Santos, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Fechette, Myles, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Furtado, Ce1so, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Grases, Pedro, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Hah, Chong-Do (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Hirschman, Albert, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Iglesias, Enrique, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Illich, Ivan, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Kaplan, Marcos, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Jaguaribe, Helio, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Juliao, Franciso, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Karst, Kenneth, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Katz, Frederick, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Kennedy, Ian, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Kenworthy, Eloon G., 1971 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Klein, Robert, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Lacerda, Carlos, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Lombardi, Mary, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Mendes, Candido, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Narayanan, Rangachari, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Perlman, Janice, 1973 Jan 26 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Rosenbaum, H. Jon, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Sharp, Daniel, 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Skiles, Jacqueline, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Taylor, Mary, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Tulchin, Joseph S., 1975 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Turnet, Victor, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Tuthill, John, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1984-023
  - Manchester-SP: Invitation Letter (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Manchester-SP: Notes and statements (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Manchester-SP: Funding letters (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - SU - Conference Nexus (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - M-SP: Publicity (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - SP/Manchester - Time Schedule (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Phones, addresses M-SP (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Manchester-SP: Statement (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - M-SP Schedule and Arrangements (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Manchester-SP Statement (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Air Ticket Letters (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Dispensa do deposito compulsorio (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Manchester-SP: film and art component (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Travel Arrangements (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Manchester-SP: Invitees correspondence (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Manchester-SP Background, working papers (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Things sent to Wirth / Summer 1976 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Bibliography - Manchester-SP (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Conference Visitors (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Manchester - Sao Paulo Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Dieppe, Bill (Ahnaden) (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Tinker Grant (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Conference Final Budget (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Manchester-SP: Budget (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Unfiled Items (Letters) (Box 1)
  - M-S Paulo (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Unfiled Items (Many) (Box 1)
  - CLAS Endowment Fund (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Gifts and Prospects, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Gift Opportunities (GSO), 1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - NEH Challenge Grant - CRIS (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Fundraising Brochure (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Personnel Vitae/info (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Confidential (Box 2)
  - Faculty Summer Grants/Research (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - NDEA - Proposal for Center rejected, 1979 May (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - SPICE, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - LAS budget planning, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Latin-Amererican Studies 160 Political Interpretation of Chile (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - The Brazilianists - Generation of the 1960s (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Gifts, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Tentative Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Center Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Bildner Lecture Series (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Cuba Contacts, 1978-1979; 1983 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - African Studies (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Program Statements - LAS (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Spanish and Portuguese Dept., 1977; 1983 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Vortiee (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Summer Seminar - NEH (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Soccis Films (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Budget 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Projects - upcoming (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Alumni in Latin America - article (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Peru Program (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Latin American Search Committee (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Kathleen Durham (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Current Funding Options (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Caribbean Studies (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Finance Conference (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Latin American Contacts, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Bechtel International Center (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Outreach - Citizens Ed. (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Library: Technical Information Service (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Japan Conference (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - LAMP (Libraries) (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Aspen Institute (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Onward and Upward (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Fundraising, Foreign (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Thinker Foundation - Martha Muse Ragen/Reynolds (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Pub Health Program (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - LAS (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Freshman Tutorial (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Conference Ideas (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Hoover Institution, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Bolivar House - status of, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Unfiled Material (Newsletters) (Box 2)
  - ESAN (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Functionalist/Sp. Relationship debate (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Brazil Symposium (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Multi-National Corps (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Japan Contacts (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Universidad de los Andes - Stanford (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Gary How project on Brazil State and Agriculture (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Hovey Clark (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Tinker Foundation, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Tinker Foundation - Summer Research Grants (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Inter-American Foundation, Peter Bell new President (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Luce Foundation (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Heritage Foundation, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Gavin, John (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Black, William (Bi11) (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Cargil Foundation (via Jed Hepworth) (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Iberian Foundations (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Hewlett Foundation (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Tinker Fellows (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Pete Sylvester (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Lyman involvement (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Raymund W. Sanders (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Funding - Key Memos (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - LAS - Fundraising goals 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Friends of Latin America (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Garrit Vander Ende (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Funding Leads (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Francisco Bravo (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Brazil business directories and ties (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - International Systems Research (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - International Relations (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - REAL (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Schools Program (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Unfiled Materials (Many) (Box 3)
  - Fundraising Brochure (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Peru - Spares, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Mexico Program, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Peru - Application Process, 1974 Feb (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - LASPA - Peru Correspondence, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Unfiled Materials (Many) (Box 3)
  - Report on Brazilian Television (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Unfiled Materials (Box 3)
  - Radio Marti (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Communications Conference (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Rogers/Antola Faculty/Student Field Research, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Caribbean Conference (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Unfiled Materials (Box 3)
  - Tinker Foundation 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Tinker Chair Invitation Letters, acceptances, etc. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Tinker Chair business, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Great Powers Sem, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Unfiled Materials (Box 3)
  - Tinker Chair - CVs (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Tinker Chair - CVs and statements (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Tinker Chair Committee notes, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Unfiled Materials (Box 3)
  - Window South (Don Goodall) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Latin American Art (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Art Department (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Art Historians and Critics - LA (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Arthur Albrecht (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Window South (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Latin Arnerican Art - Dean Chace (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Dr. Joyce Waddell Bailey (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Gildred Foundation (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Terence W. Thomas (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Franke, W. A. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Bank of America (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - John Tucker (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Rodolfo Windhausen (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Janet Crews (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - CRIS - announcements of govt programs; memos (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Jeff Morby (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - General David Parker (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Bill McKenzie, Harold Chatland (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Great Powers (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Venezuelan Chair, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Pablo Pulido (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Venezuela: Fundacion Gran Mariscal de Ayacucho (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Venezuelan Contacts - looking for a chair, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Wingspread Conference (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Title VI - Congressional actions and Pres Comm, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - USOE and LASA Lobbying, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Paul Simon (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Director's Chron File, 1981 Sep-1982 Jun (Box 4)
  - Native American States - Budget (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Native American States - Dickinson (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Aguirre Beltran (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Unfiled Materials (Letters) (Box 4)
  - Borah, Woodrow (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Calnek, Edward (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Carrasco, Pedro (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Condareo, Ramiro (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Elliott, John (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Franco, Jean (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Julien, Catherine (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Klor de Alva, Jorge (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Loekhart, James (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Karhunen, Frances (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Morris, Craig (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Morse, Richard (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Iilurra, John V. (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Orixz, Alfonso (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Pease Garcia, Franklin (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Rounds, J. (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Rowe, John H. (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Spalding, Karen (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Stern, Steve (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Sweet, David (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Waehtel, Nathan (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Zuidema, Tom (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Travel (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Name/Address Rosters (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - The Inca and Aztec States - Contract (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Native American States - Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Info Sheets - Conference (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Native American States - Current (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Native American States - Publicity (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Native American States - Invitation List (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Native American States - Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Native American States - notes (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Salomon, Frank (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Burke, Edmund (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Favre, Henri (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Hidalgo, Jorge (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Horcasistas, Fernando (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Native American States - NEH (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Instituto Gonzalo Fernandes de Oviedo - FIRE (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Unfiled Materials (letters) (Box 4)
  - CVs (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Mexico Conference, 1980 May (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Example (Box 4)
  - Energy (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Tello-Reynolds (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Immigration and Chicano Community (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Employment (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Intellectual and Public Life (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Keynote (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Border State Relations (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - M-SP Participants (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Unfiled Materials (many) (Box 5)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1985-024
  - Fulbright-Hays (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Summer Research Grants 1981 Originals and who sent to (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Unfiled papers (Box 1)
  - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Women in Arms (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Nicaragua (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Association Seminar, 1981 spring (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Symposium 5/16 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bag Lunches, Flyers, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Unfiled Papers (Box 1)
  - Latin American Visitors (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - General Paperwork 1980 Fall (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Unfiled Papers (Box 1)
  - Kathy Durham (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Unfiled Papers (Box 1)
  - Publicity (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - BraziLian Troupe, 1979 May (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Activities (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Brazilian-American Cultural Inst. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Invitations Art Show, 1981 spring (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Grad Schools (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Assoc Int'l des etudiants em sciences eeonomiques et commerciales (AIESEC) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Career Opportunities, Jobs, and Internships (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Real (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Graduate Student Fellowship Information (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Inter-American Fellowships (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Distinguished Latin American Lecturer Series (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Unfiled Papers (Box 1)
  - SUKAY (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Unfiled Papers (Box 1)
  - Ballet Folklorico de Estanford Funding Proposal (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - "I" Center Films (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Brazilian Troupe (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - IUSP BRAZIL (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Proposals Seeking Funding (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Regional Faculty Renewal Grants, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Predissertation Grants (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Unfiled Papers (Box 1)
  - Faculty Research Grants, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Winter 1981 CORE Seminar (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Faculty Field Research, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Stanford-Berkeley Grad Students (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - CORE Seminar, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Visitors, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Committees on Latin American Studies (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Publicity for 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Ken Newman (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Graduate Research Grants, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Campus Activities, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Faculty Research Grants Applications and Announcements, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Faculty-Student Research Grants, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Undergraduate Summer Grants, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Undergraduate Summer Grants, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Faculty Renewal Grants, 1981 summer (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Graduate Research Grant, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Originals of Short Term Grant Publicity, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Prof School Students Summer Field Research (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Prof School Grants, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Berkeley Latin American Studies (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Operating Budgets, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Unfiled Papers (Box 1)
  - LASA meeting, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Van Whiting course (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - LASA Bibliography (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Fulbright-Hays Doctoral Research, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Admissions, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - MA Admissions Data, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Marcia Erickson CLAS, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Committees (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Bag Lunches and Events, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - CLAS, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - CLAS Meetings (Minutes), 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - LASA Committee Members, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Nicaraguan Junta Visit, 1979 Dec 13 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Mexico conference Spring 1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Bag Lunch Series, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Cathy's Dittos (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Antonio Cruz (Brazil), 1980 Apr 9 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Bag lunches and other activities at Bolivar, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Foreign Visitors, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Foreign Visitors and Events, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Bag Lunch Series, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Bi-Centennial Lecture Series (List of Stanford Alumni Club Directory), 1975-76 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Special Seminars, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Seminar on Contemporary Latin American Problems (Reynolds) 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Program of Activities, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - LASA Bibliography (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Latin American Studies Enrollment Figures, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Course Offerings: Latin American Studies, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - LAS-Related Course Descriptions, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - LAS Courses, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Consortium of Northern California Latin Americanists (Box 2)
  - MA Graduate Students, Addresses, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - MA Prog. - A defense of, 7/70 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Graduate Students All Departments - Fellowships etc., 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - FLAS Fellowship Results, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Graduate Admissions l980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Graduation Lists, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - CLAS, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - LAS Brochure, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Brochure, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Brochure - Working Paper (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Brochure, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Old Brochures (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Tinker Summer Research Grant (Box 3)
  - Ford Report, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Ford Report Working File, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Ford Report, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - REAL (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Stanford - Berkeley Report, 1973 Feb (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Career Report, LAS Graduates, 1973-1978 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - MA and BA Ernployment stats. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - LAS MA Employment/Grad. School Survey, 1973 Feb (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - LAS Ph.D. Students, in departments (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Placement of Latin Americanist Ph.D. Candidates, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Placement of LAS Ph.D.s (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Readings for LAS 80 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous articles (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Copies of articles for 1982; changes to reader (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - 1982 Masters (not used in 1983) (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - 8A Cohen; readings (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - LAS 80 Reading Packet, 1989 spring (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Wirth, John D., Course Evaluation (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Articles used in 1981 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Culture, Politics, and Society in Latin America (Box 3)
  - Latin America, Its Problems and Its Promise (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1985-099
  - NEH Summer Seminar (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Nicaraguan Consulate (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Zellerbach (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bank of America - BJS Siegel (Material taken to meeting in SF), 1975 Apr 7 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bank of America Consortium (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Presentations - LAS (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - LASA/USOE (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - LASA Meetings Nov 14-16 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Atlanta LASA Meetings March 25, 26, 27, 28; Rocky Mountain Council of LA New Mexico (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - LASA (National) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - NDEA/LAS Proposal Evaluation 1976 NDFL (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - L975 - LASPAU Wirth, J.D. Director (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Japan - Clas (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Old LAS Files at Archives, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Personnel General (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Staff - Unemployment Insurance (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Staff - Opportunities/Openings PER (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Council for International Exchange 1974 and on (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Ga1l, Norman, Letter from Rodonia Parts 1-5 LAS 80 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Letter from Rodonia Parts 1-5 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Unfiled Material (Box 1)
  - Letter from Rodonia Parts 1-5 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Letter from Rodonia Parts 1-5 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Letter from Rodonia Parts 1-5 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Letter frorn Rodonia Parts 1-5 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - LAS 80 Hist 80 PS 123D Course Reader (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - LAS 80 Hist 80 PS 123D Course Reader (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - LAS 80 Course Reader Culture, Politics, and Society in LA (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Unfiled Material (Box 1)
  - SU - UCB Library Effort (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - NDEA Title VI information general (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Summer in Latin America Programs, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Exxon Foundation (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - USOE Title VI attempts to save (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - USOE and LASA Fall Lobbying, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Commission to examine crisis of L and area studies, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - INTL Studies Title VI Tim Wirth (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - President's Commission (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - President's Commission - Ward Draft (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Presidents - Kissinger, Matthews, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Riley - Shea Report (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Center Directors Meetings (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Riordan Roett - correspondence, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Wingspread Meetings - Center Directors, 1979 Feb (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - LASA Clasp report - supporting documents: Glade, Riley, Roett, Wirth (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Ford Foundation, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Tinker Foundation, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Lou Goodman Draft for Pres. Comm., 1979 Apr (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Delano, William A. - correspondence, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - LASA Executive Council (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Ed Meador - USOE (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - NDEA Action Letters 1977 NDFL (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - USOE Group Programs Abroad (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - LASA - Pittsburgh (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - NDFL's, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - NDEA/NDFL Nat'1 Results, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - NDFL for 1977 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - NDFL Proposal 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - FLAS Ratings, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - REAL - Units (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - REAL, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - REAL, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Fundacao Biblioteca Patricia Bildner (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Spice (Box 2, Folder 5)